# Natalie Man

hello@nataliehman.co.uk • linkedin.com/in/nataliehman • www.nataliehman.co.uk

## **UX Designer**

As a UX Designer with a front-end development background, I combine my interest in technology and problem-solving skills to create product experiences that meet business goals and user needs. I have collaborated with developers in an agile environment to understand technological capabilities and use design thinking to develop impactful solutions.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

### **UX Designer**

**UX Playground •** Jul 2018 - Present

- Created content strategies, user flow diagrams, wireframes and prototypes for rebranding the company website, which increased visitor traffic from 60% to 151% within 6 months.
- Collaborated with the community founder on design research, and created presentations for events such as Adobe MAX 2018, Brand Week Istanbul and Berlin Design Week.
- Supported the team in organising events and training for the design community, which grew by over 3,700 members in 3 years.

## **UX Designer (Contract)**

Adobe • Nov 2021 - Dec 2021

- Conducted user research on workshop topics to help Adobe's XDI team to promote XD to its enterprise customers and boost software adoption.
- Collaborated with a Senior UX Designer to develop two "CMD+cause" remote design workshops for Adobe's enterprise customers. Each workshop session achieved up to 100 registrations.
- Crafted presentations in Adobe XD and developed activities on audience engagement tools like Mentimeter, enabling Adobe's XDI team to facilitate productive workshop sessions.

### **UX Designer**

Smartology.net • Feb 2018 - Apr 2019

- Conducted 5 user interviews to identify the needs of internal users, and communicated these actionable insights to the engineering team for improving workflow efficiency.
- Organised usability testing with the Lead Front-End Developer for an automated tool
  that helps account managers to efficiently create screenshots of ad campaigns for
  clients.
- Facilitated ideation sessions with 11 team members, including a product owner, account managers, and engineers, which led to a redesigned dashboard to support the company's growth.

### **Front-End Developer**

Smartology.net • Nov 2014 - Feb 2018

- Developed the company's WordPress website with consistent branding, and created a process for the sales and marketing team to publish blog posts.
- Managed over 60 client ad campaigns and designed over 2000 creative ads.
   Process includes research, creating mock-ups, managing client feedback, building and testing.
- Worked in a team of 3, and conducted peer reviews to assess the quality of ad campaigns before launching on media publishing websites such as Financial Times, BBC and Bloomberg.

## Web/Graphic Designer and Marketing Assistant

GetOptics Group Ltd • Oct 2011 - Mar 2012

#### **SKILLS**

Agile, Content strategy, Prototyping, Usability testing, User-centered design, User interviews, User research, Wireframing

#### **EDUCATION & TRAINING**

#### **Project UX 2.0**

UX Playground • Aug 2017 - Jun 2018

## Master of Arts (MA) in Web Design & Content Planning

University of Greenwich • Sep 2012 - Jul 2014

## Bachelor of Science (BSc) in Computer Science

Queen Mary, University of London • Sep 2007 - Jul 2010